DANIEL SANCHO JARA

Front-End Web Specialist Developer & Back-End Web Intermediate level

CONTACT

d.sancho.23@hotmail.com

+34 644743458

Valencia, Spain 💿

LinkedIn in

Github (

4

EDUCATION

Web Application Development
Professional Training
IES Conselleria
2017 - 2018
Valencia, Spain

Networks and Microcomputer Systems Medium Training IES Conselleria 2015 - 2016 Valencia, Spain

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Languajes

HTML CSS

SCSS

JavaScript

PHP

MySQL + MariaDB

Git

TypeScript

ABOUT ME

I am passionate about web design, experienced in Front-End Web with a high level in database management and an intermediate level in Back-End Web development, with proven experience at Infortisa S.L. developing and maintaining Web applications with documented and reusable code. I love to learn and develop new things, and I am always willing to face new challenges and difficulties, including learning new frameworks or structures. In general, most Front-Ends tend to follow a pattern, adopting the styles, templates and tools already established and I, in addition to that, am the one who defines all that structure, thus being able to create templates from scratch, or adapt to an already established design.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

My objective is to bring both my potential and my knowledge to a company that helps me grow both personally and professionally.

• These last two years I have been working from home, and I consider that it is the way in which I feel most motivated and in which I can best exploit my capacity, so it is what I am looking for most in a company right now.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

INFORTISA S.L.

June 2018 - current / Valencia

- Desarrollo y diseño de aplicaciones Web Responsive
- Web Application maintenance
- Database management
- Creating and maintaining Ajax with PHP
- Creating and maintaining models and controllers with PHP
- Optimization, explanation and reusability of the code
- Task management through Freedcamp or Youtrack, with Kanban methodology
- Version control with Git

Libraries and Standards

jQuery JWT MVC Smarty Youtrack, Freedcamp

Frameworks

Ionic (Cordova, Capacitor, WebApp)

Angular

Custom MVC with .htaccess and redirection to controllers

Operative Systems

Windows (7, 8, 10) Linux (Ubuntu) Guided, instructed and helped in a teleworking environment to 8 Junior programmers and 1 Intermediate programmer incorporated into the Development team, both in Front-End and Back-End methodologies. In the development, a series of 10 practical exercises were designed so that they could gain practice with our working metodology.

Web Development Coordinator

INFORTISA S.L.

January 2021 - December 2021 / Valencia

• Project leader and team coordinator, with 3 co-workers under my lead.

Mobile Development with Angular & Ionic

INFORTISA S.L.

February 2021 - June 2021 / Valencia

- Development and design of native android application from scratch with Cordova.
- Documented operation and code of the application.